<p bold="true">Benanov's Sarcastic Questbook</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p space="2"/>
      <link ref="index" color="#CC3333">&lt;- Index</link>
      
<p>You all wanted a quest book. This is not the quest book you deserve, but it's the quest book you need.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">STONE AGE</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find rocks and sticks.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You can make stone tools. Get banging.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Cut some grass and look for plants near the water that can assist in the creation of a straw hat. Oddly enough, the reeds required only grow in colder climates.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: It looks silly, but it will keep you cooler.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Throw a log, three sticks down on the ground, and some straw, then light it</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A fire. That and you can now tell Prometheus, "new phone who dis"</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: kill a cow, a horse, a dire wolf (hah), a bear, or other large animal for a Large Hide. Place atop two thatch blocks.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: a bed that sets your spawn point, so you don't have to run south from spawn every time you die.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find some seeds.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Straight out of the late 90's, it's co-ed naked farming: grab a hoe and plant your seed.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Figure out which key is used to place objects on the ground so you can build your first pit kiln.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: it's V. The V key. Now make me a pretty pot. Dye it black, because we know you've been killing squid for food.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">COPPER AGE</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find some copper ore.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Copper Saw. Look, I know you all want to make a pick first...</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find some more copper ore.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Okay, NOW you can make a pick.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Even more copper ore.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A storage problem. Easily solved by making chests. THIS time.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find Basalt, Andesite, Rhyolite, or one of the other igneous rocks</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Stone Anvil.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>PRO TIP: Anything made with Basalt looks like ass.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find Flux-bearing stone - Limestone, Dolomite, or Marble. Grind it. Make flux.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You can weld ingots! There's no weld button - You shift-right-click on the anvil with a hammer in your hand to weld ingots together.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Flux + water = limewater; log + water = tannin. Soak, scrape, re-soak, and tan leather.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Black pajamas, bellows, a halter, and a saddle - you're dressed for a date, too bad it's with a horse.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Kill a Bear, Cow, Horse or Llama (depending on your butchery skill) until you get a Bladder. Make a leather water flask.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Significantly less cursing due to jug breakage; significantly more cursing when your flask breaks and you realize that was your last bladder.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a leather forging bib.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Not having to stand in water to forge.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Scare up 1400 units of copper and make an anvil.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A sense of pride and accomplishment, and the ability to weld those 14 bronze ingots you've stacked over in the corner immediately afterward.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a horse grindstone</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Higher grain yields! No one starves! Yay! Plus the endless entertainment of watching a horse go in a circle.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Get high; Y > 170; and find Hemp</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Rope and Fishing Bait</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a BWM vertical windmill and a millstone.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>OPTIONAL QUEST: Make a horizontal windmill and then realize you need Gold to make gearboxes</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: not having to scrape leather manually; deafness from the CONSTANT GRINDING NOISE</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">BRONZE AGE</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find Bismuth and Zinc; Gold and Silver; or Tin.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Bronze (that you were making anyway)</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Bronze axe.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You are now sentenced to chopping down hundreds of trees in order to make enough charcoal to afford to use that new Bloomery.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find Graphite and Kaolinite.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You can now post "I found graphite!" on r/technode or on the discord, because really - it's an accomplishment. That and you can burn a pile of it on fire clay for now, and later you'll burn out all your Kaolinite Floo Powder teleporting back and forth between your summer plantation and your winter home every 30 seconds because you forgot something, and all your graphite will be used in a Nuclear Reactor. Savor this moment, miner. Savor it, for it is quick to sublimate.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make fire clay</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: not having to use a pit kiln to mix bronze, allowing you to screw it up in new and exciting ways.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a plow.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Add shovels to it and you can leave evidence of your bad driving, in the form of paths; waste stone on 3 hoes to plow farmlands quickly, or just drag it empty over tall grass to mow the lawn. Unfortunately this quest book does not come with a friendly neighborhood 11-year-old to mow your lawn, you gotta do it yourself.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make Waystones using red gems and gold. Place waystone, give it a name. Make signposts, give them a name that matches the waystone name. Teleport from the sign to the waystone for a price of 1 Kaolinite Powder + 1 per 500m distance.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Watching your basemates deplete your Kaolinite supplies on corpse runs and needless back and forth fetch trips just before you finish making all the things that require fire clay.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>That and now all your roads are somewhat less useful, which is why the plow quest was put first.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a BWM saw</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Higher wood yields, a new death message</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">IRON AGE</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make an iron anvil.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You could go after that achievement where you make 4 pieces of iron armor and wear it, but honestly don't bother, you'll get iron from mob drops later. Just make a blast furnace.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a horse chopping block and a horse press</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Chopping block - Higher wood yields without the possibility of death.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Press - Paper! You can also get creosote oil early, which is nice at this stage of the game, but when you make a coke oven later you'll just have even more of a storage problem. However, you can use your nice new creosote oil to make Treated Wood Barrels.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a hopper</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: TPS lag</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make an Iron Water Flask</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Your flask now holds two buckets of water (or milk), and lasts long enough to you to forget where you put the bladders. You can also use it to see how full a steel tank is when an update clobbers your WAILA settings.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>However, we all know it's yet another thing that sits in your hotbar while you drink out of ponds.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">STEEL AGE</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make the blast furnace block, anywhere between 12 and 60 wrought iron sheets, and a Tuyere.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Tinnitus, and a new vocabulary word to share with your friends at school when you can go again</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a blast furnace with a Crucible underneath. Spend 5 minutes pumping bellows, or pump only once in a while, or whatever that newfangled trick is that you can do in 1.12; I just wedge a coffee mug on the right mouse button of my trackball and go use the bathroom or something</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Steel</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make rudimentary RF power now that you can build an IE windmill</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You can power your refrigerator</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a refrigerator</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Food will survive you logging out on a multiplayer server</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a TFC Tech Crucible</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You can slow down a bit on the tree farm there, Paul Bunyan, you don't need as much charcoal now.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a TFC Tech Electric Forge</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: all your meat is now perfectly cooked at 200 C, cheap glass blocks, and efficient metal heating</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make Storage Drawers</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: An actual solution to your growing pile of storage problems</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">COLORED STEEL AGE</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find Nickel</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Now you can actually get to the good part of the pack. Reflect on how long it took you to find Nickel.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Mix up some Red and Blue Steel</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Freezing in the night time, but you now have a fighting chance in the Nether (Red Steel Armor)...and now you'll overheat in your own buildings in the Winter (Blue Steel Armor)</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Craft an "Ultimate" (Vanilla) bucket.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: OMFG it's a vanilla bucket, you've won TFC! Now you can take ponds with you and drink out of them instead of using your flask. Sure you could do this with a red steel bucket, but now you don't have to use a separate bucket just for lava. Saved 100% inventory space over the TFC solution! BAM!</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>PRO TIP: Your victory is also short-lived when you see how many recipes call for a vanilla bucket and don't give it back to you.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Nether Portal with your new black steel pick.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Glowstone, netherrack, quartz, and a sense that you should have brought your black bronze armor</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>PRO TIP: Don't anger the pigmen. Yet.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a fort and make that a gold farm using your disused vertical windmill and saw.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: The joyous sound of Zombie Pigmen queuing to "use" the saw while you slowly dehydrate, hiding in your fort from the ghasts. It's beautiful, really.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>PRO TIP: Zombie Pigmen adore snowball fights</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">IMMERSIVE ENGINEERING AGE</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Metal Press</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: never having to weld two ingots EVER AGAIN.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Crusher</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Never using a Quern again. Also, Tinnitus in your other ear.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>PRO TIP: Don't eat the horse that powers your horse grindstone.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Pumpjack</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: The crushing realization that you're going to need to make a distillation tower for this, or at least a refinery</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Petroleum distillation tower</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Lowered property values as your village is next to an industrial park</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Squeezer, a Fermenter, and a Refinery</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You can now stop throwing out all your rotten food</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Diesel Generator</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Tinnitus in both ears and your entire household</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a mining drill</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Mining 9 unsupported blocks at a time is almost a guaranteed cave-in</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Farm Ghast Tears. Find Nether Wart. Make a Mixer, a TFC Tech Smeltery, a Blowpipe, and a Bottler. Oh, you'll need Rainwater too, see Rockhounding quests for details, only because I hate repeating myself</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Regeneration Extended (Wart -> Tear -> Redstone) is the best healing item in the game. You're gonna be sucking these down like it's your first night in Las Vegas, so make a bunch.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>PRO TIP: Ghasts love snowball fights just as much as Zombie Pigmen do!</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a solar tower and some mirrors.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: The realization that you're a vampire because you can't see yourself in the mirror</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a Steam Turbine</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: The Tinnitus is now at "Baby Driver" levels.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>BONUS ACTION: Remembering that movie exists. Sorry not sorry.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make an Extractor. Dig out all blocks around the wheel. PUT A ROOF OVER IT THAT ISN'T RIGHT NEXT TO THE WHEEL. One slab height is not enough, has to be a full block's worth of space.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Multiple server crashes - Did you only do the first thing I said? We're not kidding. The extractor is a crashy bitch in TFC worlds. Do it right and you are rewarded.</p>
<p>With a storage problem.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">PNEUMATIC CRAFT</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find sulfur</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Not having to kill creepers for gunpowder</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a pressure chamber</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Not having to blow up your iron</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a refinery</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You weren't using those diamonds anyway. Diamonds aren't a girl's best friend; plastic is.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make an Amadron tablet</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: When you get the pun</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make an assembly line</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: 20 bar and the ability to produce pressure with RF</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Rockhounding Precipitation Chamber and make Sodium Polyacrylate. You might have to come back to this one.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You can make snow on demand any time of the year. Oh, that and Etching Acid. Yep, we gated the second half of PneumaticCraft behind Rockhounding. You're welcome.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make an OpenBlocks Glider with your brown plastic and Sodium Polyacrylate</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You have been cursed to never having it on your hotbar while falling.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make PnC Armor. Become immune to temperature effects.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Finding out that the AR Space Suit (which is possibly cheaper) also does this.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">ROCKHOUNDING</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a SimplyLoaders Raintank to start Rainwater Collection.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Water water everywhere but not a drop to drink. It's Vanilla Water!</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>PRO TIP: Do not for any reason stack two SimplyLoaders Raintanks on top of each other. No. Really. Not kidding. Your world will not stop crashing the server unless you use external tools. I fixed this bug 7 months ago as of this writing and they still haven't merged it on Github.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make the TFC Tech Smeltery</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: remembering Tinker's Construct is not in the pack as you make glass bottles</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Slurry Pond, a Gasifier Burner, Gas Purifier, and Two Power Stations. Make Syngas.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: I SPENT ALL THAT IRON ON THIS?!</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Mineral Sizer</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: All the Gangue you can carry, which means Chunkloaders.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>PRO TIP: Rockhounding Power Stations can use Charcoal and Lava (and possibly other burnables) as "Fuel" - this sounds good, until you realize exactly how inefficient using Charcoal is compared to making that Charcoal into Syngas.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Lab Oven, an ElectroChemical CSTR, 4x Evaporation Tanks, a Leaching Controller, and another Gasifier Burner for Water Vapor. (Phew). Make Sulfuric Acid, then Hydrochloric Acid in your Lab Oven. Make Sodium Hydroxide in your CSTR. Realize that you need a good source of Rainwater. Turn Gangue into Shards.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Multiple industrial accidents and two new storage problems - holy crap that's a lot of shards, and that's a lot of leachate</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Retention Controller, a NuclearCraft Rock Crusher, a NuclearCraft Electrolyzer, a NuclearCraft Chemical Reactor, and beg/borrow/steal some way to Hydrofluoric Acid. Turn your leachate into more shards.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: The realization that 200mb of High-Grade Leachate turns into 1000mb of Toxic Waste, and an even bigger storage problem - none of these shards are the same as the other ones I made earlier</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Chemical Extractor, a Reforming Tower, and a NuclearCraft Chemical Reactor. Also a NuclearCraft Nitrogen Collector</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: turn all your shards into Metal Dusts, and a new storage problem - where am I gonna put all this Cadmium and Phosphorous, and what is this Lutetium stuff anyway</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Metal Alloyer</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Actual upgraded filters on your leachate controller & retention controller, so you can actually choose the shard you want instead of the "all of them" setting you're using currently</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Oh wow I can make Colored Steel in this?</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Oh I can make Wrought Iron at the cost of 1 charcoal per 10 ingots? Pinch me</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Speed upgrades and more industrial accidents as you realize you tuned your pipe network around the slow machine speeds</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">NuclearCraft</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find a pitchblende vein</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Nickel 2.0™</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>BONUS ACTION: At least Granite rocks are prettier than Gabbro.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Mine some pitchblende</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Guys is radiation bad?</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Throw the pitchblende into your crusher</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: One pitchblende crushes into 9 Uranium Dust, netting you enough nuclear material to power a small country for a year. For you, it won't be enough.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>PRO TIP: Get a spot in the Treaty on the Non-Proliferation of Nuclear Weapons.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>BONUS ACTION: If you're on the official test server, hit me up for some Rad-Away. I might have you gather mushrooms though. My base glows in the dark but it's not from the radiation.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make some basic plating</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Empty space in your Graphite and Lead storage</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make an Alloy Furnace</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: The realization that all of your Black Steel is going to make Ferroboron</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: make a Geiger Counter</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Glorious silence...for now</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make some Advanced plating</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Empty space in your Lithium and Redstone storage</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: make a Universal Bin</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Looks prettier than a trashcan next to your Turbine. Silicon Carbide being an ingot will remind you Mekanism isn't in the pack</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Separator</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A new storage problem; this is the one where all the things are radioactive</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make some Depleted Uranium plating</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: non-zero radiation levels</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make some Elite Plating</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Actually making a Radiation Scrubber</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make some rad-away fluid</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Glowing yellow mushrooms all over your base</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make Light Radiation Shielding</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Now you can make Medium Radiation Shielding</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make Medium Radiation Shielding</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Now you can make Heavy Radiation Shielding</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make Heavy Radiation Shielding and apply it to your Space Suit or PnC Armor</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Not dying in 15 seconds after picking up Prometheum by accident</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Find Manganese, Magnesium, and Boron</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: More ingots to store in a chest somewhere; also you can make batteries and the turbine</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Mine a lot of Zirconium and make -ZA fuel</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: If you don't have at least 3 stacks of Zirconium dust AFTER alloying all your fuel, repeat this quest until you do</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Completely deplete 3 nearest Zirconium veins to power your thirsty IE Excavator</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A reminder to look at JEI, because NuclearCraft's Rock Crusher has a chance to turn Diorite rocks into Zirconium dust. Thankfully you hoarded all mined cobblestone in these handy storage drawers instead of throwing it all away eve̵r̶y̷ ̸t̵i̸m̴ë̴̙́,̷͔̓ ̸̼͆r̴̺͊i̵͇͋ḡ̸̨ḩ̸̛̮̹̮̖̺̯̞͛̈́́̈́͑͌̓͠ţ̷̹͓̠͇͓͈̱̂́̈́ͅ?̴̺̝̙̹̈́̀ ̶̢͖̱͈͖̠̜͕̱͗͠R̶̡̳͈͎̼͓͈͓͎͚̭̦͖̗͍̼̮̖͚̗͓̳̥͕̬̗̱̦̳̺͓͍͍̣̼̿͂́̀̿̏͐́̏̓̏̒̈͐̀̀̈͒̆̓͠I̴̢̧̢̛̤͈̙͙̹̬̦̠͕̳͖͚̰͌̔̾̈̓̈́̀̃̔̂̓͛̈̇́̊̃́́̃̕̕͜͠͝͠͠ͅĢ̴̡̧̢̛͈̳̣̘̠͈̪̯̗̖͚̪̮͔͎͓̦͔͚̳͇͍̳̖̬̣̣̱̗̔̉̊͂͊͋̓͂̔̃̌̿͌̀̒̅͊̂͌͆̅̽͗̅̕͝͠͝Ḩ̴̛̜̗͙̰͉̲̥̜̀̏̐̌̀̀̒̈̔̓̊̿̈́̀́̓̚T̷̨̠̻̰̖̝͕̥͉͍̖̯̰̹͗͜ͅ?̴̧̪̝͙̳̱͆̈́͛͘͠</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Decay Hastener</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Oh crap that released radiation into the world? WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make some radium neutron sources</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: 90% efficiency (up from 0%)</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make Upgraded Power Storage</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Does the tier 3 battery really leak radiation into the world? (YES, but it's a small amount.)</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a Compact Water Source</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: a crushing realization you can't easily and sustainably convert Rain Water into Fresh Water</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a Dense Water Source</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: An understanding of what few things Rainwater is used for</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make Heavy Water and fill some Empty Frames with it</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A smugness that you can build heavy water moderators whereas in most packs with NuclearCraft everyone is stuck using Beryllium and Graphite. That smugness is soon tempered by the realization that there is no efficiency bonus.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build an XNet controller and a few advanced connectors to shuttle power and HPS around</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Lagging the server for a good 30 seconds with a single shift-click</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a Reactor Controller and Fuel Cells</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A sparkly new bucket of Corium</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a working nuclear reactor</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>2 hours on YouTube later...</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: One! Two! Three! Four! Four Buckets of Corium! Ah, ah, ah.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a Turbine. Hook universal bin to output port.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: 13691 RF/t</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Make a Fuel Reprocessor</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: a chest full of 1-8 depleted fuel pellets of various types</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Mine some Thorium</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A couple of hours of frustration sitting in front of the NC Reactor Planner trying to make a decent Irradiator Design</p>
<p>PRO TIP: Yes, if you put Thorium in your Rockhounding Chemical Extractor you *will* get more Thorium than just combining it into scrap. I would consider cranking the Intensity to 16. (I usually leave it at 10 for Nice Round Numbers™, it's profitable even at 10.)</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Turn Thorium into Protactinium-Enriched Thorium (TBP), turn that into TBU, then use that as fuel and reprocess it</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Neptunium and a new pretty color of isotopes to store (Neptunium is required to complete the tech tree.)</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Turn bismuth into Polonium, make some Po-Be sources</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Radiation sickness and 95% efficiency</p>
<p>BONUS ACTION: This is one of the more useful deadly things you've made</p>
<p>PRO TIP: It takes longer to make Polonium than TBP. Be patient.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Melt sugar into molten sugar, mix with water in Chemical Reactor to make Ethanol</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Nuclear Exclusion Zone around your Base (This bug was fixed)</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">ADVANCED ROCKETRY</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a Lathe</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Making pistons without heating metal is its own reward.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build an Electrolyzer</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A new interesting storage problem and the ability to fill up the Oxygen in your space suit so it doesn't look like a lit cigarette</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a Cutting Machine</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Highest yield cutting planks, and a new death message because you can't stop standing on it</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a Chemical Reactor</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Silicon Boules</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build that processing assembly line thingie</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A cute little factory animation and cheaper AR crafting components for all the machines you already built</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a rolling machine</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: An inferior metal press that's stuck on "Plate" and requires water, but you're not going to space without it</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a Satellite Builder</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: We still don't know who watches the watchers, but we know who built the builder.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a launch pad</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: A complaint from the local township committee about your zoning violations</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a rocket</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: the realization that no wiki has been updated for "Bipropellant" rockets yet</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p bold="true">OPEN COMPUTERS</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build a computer case</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: You teach your kid a few new swear words when the recipe eats your 'Hard' Hammer (yes I reported it)</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: build a Screen</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Now your bird has a few chosen phrases to repeat at the screen recipe eats another hammer (reported this one too). T3 is also one of the few blocks that uses Pitchblende that isn't radioactive.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: build a Keyboard</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: now you can interact with a computer you haven't finished building yet. Appreciate the realism as you realize you have to make nearly all 101 keys yourself.</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: build a Power Convertor</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: now you can actually power the computer that won't boot yet. Curse as you realize that your computer should be moved up/down 1m and you have to break & replace everything</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: build a graphics card, CPU, ram, a hard disk, and maybe a redstone card or something</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: your raw materials chests are a little emptier, but hey, at least all the slots are filled</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: build an OpenOS disk AND an EPROM</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: IT BOOTS!</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: build a Reactor Computer Port and a Turbine Computer Port</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: Spend 3 hours looking for a program to control your reactor</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build an internet card</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: actually download and use the program</p>
      <p space="10"/>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>QUEST: Build an RS latch using designs from the minecraft wiki and use your existing XNet setup to control redstone outputs instead of this OpenComputers thingie</p>
      <p space="10"/>
<p>REWARD: about 5 hours saved